{
    "id": "7240d61c55e94ed3bc35aad889a90c65",
    "title": "Idiomatic Expressions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "To take someone under your wing is to ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hide them",
                "take care of them",
                "suffocate them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b7d7e036a6244684ac6069dfaefca5b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "To eat the humble pie is to  ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eat very little",
                "eat greedily",
                "make a humble apology"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bd18e0ab8953478395596db92ede3bac"
        },
        {
            "question": "To get out of the bed on the wrong side is to ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "injure yourself",
                "defeat yourself",
                "be in a particularly irritable mood"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "39335e3446c446bbb0e957d47971d343"
        },
        {
            "question": "To make the feathers fly is to ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cause turmoil",
                "establish peace",
                "make a lot of noise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a15baa5d2ab949dea1e4007148308233"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does itsy-bitsy mean?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "magnificent",
                "tiny",
                "soft"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1b2cc424b9c405ab8f75b850ea7bfdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "To dilly-dally is to …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have a good time",
                "waste time",
                "make good use of time"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c45c5aeca244ee2b5572e6b2746d36c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I still miss the ……………………. of university life.",
            "description": "Hurly-burly means busy activity.",
            "answers": [
                "willy-nilly",
                "wishy-washy",
                "hurly-burly"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ed5f49e3dc5749e2a217552beefa8154"
        },
        {
            "question": "To live in straitened circumstances is to live in ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "opulence",
                "poverty",
                "pain"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "16800610c48d4041a120a6737d6e6ae5"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the expression wishy-washy mean?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weak",
                "strong",
                "efficient"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b28445f85d14fc9ae07606231c3a101"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to cooperate ………………………",
            "description": "Willy-nilly means whether you like it or not. ",
            "answers": [
                "willy-nilly",
                "dilly-dally",
                "itsy-bitsy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4e82bd98e144480fb2712d09b5619681"
        },
        {
            "question": "To be at loggerheads is to ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "approve",
                "agree",
                "disagree strongly"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f032a81d13ef4f2faf227101232953da"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bete noire means an object of ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "affection",
                "admiration",
                "aversion"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7e5f1977de4f459aa84390b3d3ef7304"
        }
    ]
}